Stone walls remember what the living forget
돌벽은 산 자들이 잊은 것을 기억한다
Candles flicker where the shadows have wept
그림자들이 울었던 곳에 촛불이 깜빡인다
I walk these halls in a loop with no end
나는 끝없이 이 복도들을 맴돈다
A ghost dressed in light that the dark cannot bend
어둠이 꺾을 수 없는 빛을 입은 유령
Stained glass colors bleed across the floor
스테인드글라스 빛깔들이 바닥 위로 번진다
Every footstep echoes back to the door
발걸음마다 문까지 메아리쳐 돌아온다
I keep on searching for a way to be free
나는 자유로워질 길을 계속 찾는다
But the cathedral holds what's left of me
하지만 성당은 나의 남아있는 것을 붙잡고 있다
I haunt the silence between the bells
나는 종소리 사이의 고요를 맴돈다
A voice that rises where no one dwells
아무도 살지 않는 곳에서 울려 퍼지는 목소리
Through organ pipes and fractured light
오르간 파이프와 부서진 빛 사이로
I am the ghost of a cathedral night
나는 성당의 밤의 유령
The altar glows with a synthetic flame
제단은 인공 불꽃으로 빛난다
I am the ghost of a cathedral night
나는 성당의 밤의 유령
Let the reverb carry me away
잔향이 나를 실어 보내게 해줘
Let the bassline guide me through the grey
베이스라인이 잿빛 속을 나를 이끌게 해줘
I was never meant to disappear
나는 사라질 운명이 아니었어
I was meant to echo here
나는 이곳에 울려 퍼질 운명이었어
I haunt the silence between the bells
나는 종소리 사이의 고요를 맴돈다
A voice that rises where no one dwells
아무도 살지 않는 곳에서 울려 퍼지는 목소리
Through organ pipes and fractured light
오르간 파이프와 부서진 빛 사이로
I am the ghost of a cathedral night
나는 성당의 밤의 유령